{
    "subject": "resource/Robert_Lowry_(writer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Ohio",
    "human_readable": "Robert Lowry (writer) died in Ohio.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8690526485443115,
            "question": "Where did Robert Lowry die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8452856540679932,
            "question": "Was Robert Lowry a writer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6231420636177063,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the circumstances surrounding Robert Lowry's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6011631488800049,
            "question": "What was Robert Lowry known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5004878044128418,
            "question": "In what state did Robert Lowry pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4402628540992737,
            "question": "What type of works did Robert Lowry write?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42923906445503235,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Robert Lowry's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3369828760623932,
            "question": "Were there any notable achievements in Robert Lowry's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3148459792137146,
            "question": "Where is Robert Lowry's final resting place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2996230721473694,
            "question": "Did Robert Lowry have any famous works?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robert Lowry (writer) died in Ohio.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3748_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Robert Lowry's final resting place?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3748_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable achievements in Robert Lowry's career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3748_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Robert Lowry's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3748_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3748_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3748_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3748_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3748_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3748_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3748_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3748_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3748_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3748_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3748_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe document states that Robert Lowry died in Plainfield, New Jersey, not Ohio.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n\nThe information provided does not support the triple. According to the documents, Robert Lowry died on November 25, 1899, in Plainfield, New Jersey, USA. There is no mention of his death occurring in Ohio."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not support the statement that Robert Lowry died in Ohio. According to the provided information, Robert Lowry died on Nov. 25, 1899, in Plainfield, New Jersey."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Robert Lowry died in Plainfield, New Jersey, not Ohio.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Context information states he died in Plainfield, New Jersey.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information about Robert Lowry (writer) indicates that he was born in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, USA, and died in Plainfield, New Jersey, USA, not Ohio.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Robert Lowry died on November 25, 1899, in Plainfield, New Jersey, not Ohio.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}